Finding aid to the Rosemary Keefe papers SSC.MS.00680
Sophia Smith Collection
- Series IV. Research: Feminist Theatre, 1960-2010
  - Crow Conference on Women Playwrights - Stanford University, 1980-1984 (Box 3)
  - Womyn's Theatre Festival - Boston (1), May, 1980 (Box 3)
  - Womyn's Theatre Festival - Boston (2), May, 1980 (Box 3)
  - "Pinball" by Alison Lyssa - Australia, 1981 (Box 3)
  - Bethroot Gwynn, performance artist, 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - "Coconut" by Adele Prandini, undated (Box 3)
  - "Healin' Dirt Diner" by Mary Casey and Pamela Gray, undated (Box 3)
  - Women playwrights: interviews, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
  - Copies of interviews with women playwrights, 1979-1980 (Box 3)
  - Marty Kingsbury's interview: Wallflower Order and Spiderwoman Theatre, 1970's, 1980's (Box 3)
  - Feminist Theatres surveyed, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Feminist Theatres - correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - Feminist Theatres - correspondence, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Catalogue of Feminist Theatre - from "Chrysalis" #10, 1979 (Box 3)
  - Sofia Ramos "Do You Know Who Your Wife Is?", Victoria Rue "Cancerbodies", 1992 (Box 3)
  - "Framework" and "Blind Salome" by Sandra Shotlander, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Actors' Sorority - Kansas City, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Kate Kasten, 1983 (Box 4)
  - At the Foot of the Mountain Theatre - Martha Boesing, 1981-1986 (Box 4)
  - Martha Boesing - plays, 1979-1992 (Box 4)
  - Caravan Theatre - Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1967-1989 (Box 4)
  - "Focus on Me" by Bobbi Ausubel, 1976 (Box 4)
  - Commonplace Pageant - Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1970's (Box 4)
  - Double Edge Theatre - Boston, 1981-1983 (Box 4)
  - "Cerridwen: A Journal of Women's Theatre" - Fayetteville, Arkansas - flyer, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Emmatroupe Studio - New York City, 1970's (Box 4)
  - Lilith: A Woman's Theatre - San Francisco, 1981-1984 (Box 4)
  - Medusa's Revenge Theater - New York City, 1977-1979 (Box 4)
  - Mischief Mime - Ithica, NY, 1970's-1980's (Box 4)
  - Muse Conceptions, Inc. - Boston, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Abstracts, etc. - Women's Theatre panels, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
  - Omaha Magic Theatre on JoAnn Schmidman and Megan Terry, 1977-1984 (Box 4)
  - "Brazil Fado" by Megan Terry, 1978 (Box 4)
  - "Square Blues" by Shay Youngblood, 1993 (Box 4)
  - "The Yellow Room" by Terry Baum, 1996 (Box 4)
  - "The Blessing" by Clare Coss, 1989 (Box 4)
  - "The Lunch" by Michelle A. Gabow, 1983 (Box 4)
  - "Butch 'O My Dreams" by Sandra de Helen, 1992 (Box 4)
  - "Kudzu" by Jane Chambers, undated (Box 4)
  - "A Loch in Kop!" by Michelle A. Gabow, 1993 (Box 4)
  - WAFT "Washington Area Feminist Theatre", 1973-1979 (Box 4)
  - Feminist Theatres South, 1977-1980 (Box 4)
  - Feminist Theatres - miscellaneous papers (1), 1979-1984 (Box 4)
  - Feminist Theatres - miscellaneous papers (2), 1988-1992 (Box 4)
  - Women in Theatre Festival, March 26-30, 1986 (Box 4)
  - "The Sexual Politics of Women's Theatre: Who Needs It?" - by Rosemary Curb, Boston Women in Theatre Festival, March, 1986 (Box 4)
  - "Scenes of the Times" - WRB review of Boston Women in Theatre, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Women's One World Festival (WOW) - New York City, 1980 (Box 4)
  - Boston Women's Theatre Festival, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Women in Theatre Festival - Boston, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Women in Theatre Festival - Boston, 1988 (Box 4)
  - First International Women Playwrights Conference - SUNY, Buffalo, NY (1), 1988 (Box 4)
  - First International Women Playwrights Conference - SUNY, Buffalo, NY (2), October, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Third International Women Playwrights Conference - Adelaide, Australia, July, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Fourth International Women Playwrights' Conference - Galway, Ireland, June, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Fifth International Women Playwrights Conference - Athens, Greece, May, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Sixth Women Playwrights International Conference - Manila, Philippines, November, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Feminist Theatre Sharing Session @ Michigan Womyn's Music Festival, 1980 (Box 4)
  - National Women's Studies Association (NWSA) panel - "Women Bonding in Contemporary Drama by Women", 1980-1982 (Box 4)
  - Encompass Theatre - New York City, 1978 (Box 4)
  - Correspondence with lesbian playwrights, 1991-1992 (Box 4)
  - Feminist drama course, spring, 1981 (Box 4)
  - Feminist theater - miscellaneous, 1977-1988 (Box 4)
  - Amazon All Stars - Promo, 1996 (Box 4)
  - "Is That You Nancy" by Sandra Shotlander, 1991 (Box 4)
  - National Festival of Women's Theatre - Santa Clara, CA, May, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Feminist theatre research, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Rhode Island Feminist Theatre, 1977-1985 (Box 4)
  - Reality Theater - Rochester, NY, 1970's (Box 4)
  - Omaha Magic Theatre, 1979 (Box 4)
  - "Scarlot Harlot", undated (Box 4)
  - Sisters on Stage (La Mesa, CA), Synthaxis Theatre Company (Los Angeles, CA), 1977-1979 (Box 4)
  - Theatre of Light and Shadows - Connecticut, 1979 (Box 4)
  - Women's College Theatre (New York City), 1979-1980 (Box 4)
  - Women's Experimental Theatre, 1977-1983 (Box 4)
  - Theatre Centre, 1983-1984 (Box 5)
  - Alison Laurie, New Zealand, 1974-1990 (Box 5)
  - Australian Feminist Publications, 1994 (Box 5)
  - The Center for Research on Women (CROW), Stanford - Conference on Women Playwrights, April, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Women's Theatre, 1988 (Box 5)
  - "Sistren" publication - Jamaica, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Articles for research, 1993-2010 (Box 5)
  - Theatre in London, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Sandra Shotlander - Australian playwright, 1983-1995 (Box 5)
  - Australian literary criticism, 1991 (Box 5)
  - American Feminist Theatre - articles published, 1979-1989 (Box 5)
  - Flyers, brochures, articles, "The Gelding", and correspondence from Honor M., 1971-1994 (Box 6)
  - Muncie Star article on WomanShine theater, 1978-06-13 (Box 10)
  - Illustrated flyer-brochures for At the Foot of the Mountain theater, Minneapolis, 1978-1987 (Box 10)
  - Omaha Magic Theater brochure-flyers on workshops and productions including Megan Terry's "Babes in the Bighouse," musical about life inside a women's prison, 1974-1978 (Box 10)
  - Oversize clippings from various publications regarding women playwrights, women's theater groups and productions, 1976-2007 (Box 10)
  - Oversize poster, Womyn's Theatre Festival, Boston, 1980 (Box 10)
  - Flyer and order form for Martha Boesing plays with note to Curb, undated (Box 10)
  - Rhode Island Feminist Theatre poster for Boston production, undated (Box 10)
  - Providence, Rhode Island RIFT Theatre flyer, 1976 (Box 10)
  - National Festival of Women's Theater at Santa Cruz poster for production of "Death's Angel: Requiem for a Marriage" by Terry Baum, founder of Lilith Women's Theater, 1983 (Box 10)
  - Poster for La Mama theater season, New York City, undated (Box 10)